If you go to work, you’re probably familiar with the routine of travelling to the office, hunting for an available desk, completing your tasks and then enduring your commute home.
如果你需要上班，或许对这样的日常很熟悉：奔波着去办公室，找一张空办公桌，完成手头的工作任务，然后再忍受通勤的疲惫回家。
In many ways, it seems like an outdated working practice.
从很多方面来看，这都像是一种过时的工作模式。
And maybe that’s why more and more of us are now choosing to work from home.
或许正因如此，如今越来越多的人选择居家办公。
There are, of course, many reasons for remote working, as it is also called.
当然，这种也被称为“远程办公”的模式之所以兴起，有着诸多原因。
The demands of modern life and a desire for a better work-life balance has driven the trend, along with improved technology, which makes doing most tasks at home a doddle.
现代生活的需求、人们对更好的工作生活平衡的渴望，再加上技术的进步，共同推动了这一趋势——技术的发展让在家完成大部分工作任务变得易如反掌。
In the UK, figures from the Office for National Statistics show more than one and a half million people work from home for their main job.
英国国家统计局的数据显示，英国有超过150万人将居家办公作为自己的主业。
But, although logging on from the comfort of your sofa may appeal, especially if it’s part of a flexible working approach, some people are forced to work from home and find it hard going.
不过，尽管窝在舒适的沙发上办公听起来很诱人——尤其是作为弹性工作模式的一部分——但有些人是被迫居家办公的，而且他们觉得这种模式很难熬。
Marketing consultant Mark Black told the BBC he struggled to switch off from work when he was based solely at home.
市场营销顾问马克·布莱克告诉BBC，当他完全居家办公时，总是很难从工作状态中抽离出来。
He says: "I hated home working.
他说：“我讨厌居家办公。
You get up in the morning and stare at the same four walls, do your work, and try and clock off, but you can't."
你早上起床，面对的是一成不变的四堵墙，处理完工作后，你试图下班，但根本做不到。”
It’s true that being at home means you can’t physically leave your office behind, and as Emma Mamo from mental health charity Mind says: "Home workers don't always have the same opportunities to connect with people as their office-based colleagues.”
的确，居家办公意味着你无法真正“离开”办公室。心理健康慈善机构“心智”的艾玛·马莫也表示：“居家办公的员工，并不总能像办公室同事那样，拥有同等的人际交流机会。”
But remote working doesn’t always mean being at home.
但远程办公并不等同于必须待在家里。
Cafes and workplace spaces offer a chance for workers, particularly self-employed people, to come together and interact with each other.
咖啡馆和共享办公空间为职场人——尤其是自由职业者——提供了相聚交流的机会。
There are also employees who have no choice but to work remotely because their companies have decided to do away with offices altogether to have a more agile workforce - it's certainly very cost effective and attractive for start-ups.
还有一些员工之所以不得不远程办公，是因为他们的公司为了打造更灵活的团队，决定彻底撤销实体办公室。这种模式无疑性价比很高，对初创企业来说颇具吸引力。
But for those employed by businesses with a physical base, working at home provides a convenient alternative to the 9 to 5.
而对于那些受雇于有实体办公地点的公司的员工而言，居家办公是朝九晚五通勤模式之外的一种便捷选择。
And without the distraction of their colleagues, it can be the most productive place to work!
而且没有了同事的干扰，家也能成为最高效的办公场所！